Guide to the George Borchardt Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: 1957-1984
  - ENGLISH LANGUAGE AUTHORS
    - Webster, Harriet -- Weidenfeld: Young Historian -- Wenn, Leslie -- Westwood, Jennifer -- Wheatcroft, Harry -- White, A. -- Whiter, Leonard -- Wickman, J.W. -- Wilkinson, G. -- Williams, Neville -- Woodman, Dorothy -- Woodward, Edward -- Wright & Swift -- Young, Pete (Box 264)
    - Agreement with Chelsea House -- Barrie & Jenkins: Antique Series -- Barrie & Jenkins: Arms and Armor -- Barrie & Jenkins: Church Music -- Barrie & Jenkins: Ghost Books -- Barrie & Jenkins: Illustrated Guides -- Barrie & Jenkins: Victorian Collector Series -- Barrie & Jenkins: World Coin Catalogue -- Barrie & Rockliff: Explorations -- Barrie & Rockliff: German Literature Series -- Blond: 1981 -- Bolt & Watson: Gash: 1979, 1982 -- Bolt & Watson: General: 1982 (Box 265)
    - Bolt and Watson: Lemarchand, E.: 1982 -- Bolt and Watson: Macksey: 1979 -- Hutchinson, Alan: Biology Series -- Hutchinson, Alan: Christie's Review -- Hutchinson, Alan: Encyclopedia -- Hutchinson, Alan: General: 1985 -- Hutchinson, Alan: Popular Dogs: Arco -- Hutchinson, Alan: Popular Dogs: other (Box 266)
    - Hutchinson, Alan: Rendell: 1981 -- Hutchinson, Alan: The Year's Art -- Leresche: Deacon, Richard -- Leresche: Keneally, Thomas: 1979-1980 -- Leresche: Rule, Jane: 1979 (Box 267)
    - Miscellaneous: 1981-1982 -- Rogers, Deborah: Buckman, Peter 1975 -- Rogers, Deborah: 1978-1983 -- Rogers, Deborah: McEwan: 1977 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Bragg: 1971-1978 (Box 268)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: Dead or Languishing -- Simon, Richard Scott: Fleetwood: 1972-1976 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Fisher: 1976-1978 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Gilbert, Harriet: 1972-1976 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Heald, Tim: 1972-1976, 1979 (Box 269)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: Hill, Susan: 1972-1975 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Hobson, Sarah: 1979 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Kenyon: 1976, 1979-1980 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Lewis, Norman -- Simon, Richard Scott: Offerings: N-Z: 1979-1980 -- Simon, Richard Scott: England: A-M: 1983 (Box 270)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: N-Z: 1983 -- Simon, Richard Scott: A-Z: 1984 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Slaughter: 1977-1978 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Stevenson, Christopher Sinclair -- Simon, Richard Scott: Stow -- Simon, Richard Scott: Correspondence: 1977-1978 (Box 271)
    - Vernon, Victoria: 1978 -- Vernon, Victoria: Butterworth: 1976-1979 -- Watson: Christie, Anne: 1984 -- Watson-Little: Banks, Lynne Reid: 1984 (Box 272)
    - Watt, A.P., 1975 -- Watt, Aldis Brian, 1972, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1980-1985 -- (Box 273)
    - Watt, A. P.: Alter: 1977 -- Watt, A. P.: Bermant: 1975, 1977 -- Watt, A. P.: Blake, Quentin: 1982 -- Watt, A. P.: Dead and Languishingf -- Watt, A. P.: De Bono: 1973 -- Watt, A. P.: Dickison, Peter: 1982 (Box 274)
    - Watt, A. P.: Goodfield: General -- Watt, A. P.: June 1978 -- Watt, A. P.: June 1982 -- Watt, A. P.: Graves, Robert: 1982 -- Watt, A. P.: Hamilton, Elizabeth: 1976 -- Watt, A. P.: Maddox, Brenda: 1975, 1977, other (Box 275)
    - Watt, A. P.: Maddox, Brenda: 1978-1979 -- Watt, A. P.: McCarthy, Patrick: 1977, other -- Watt, A. P.: Johnson -- Watt, A. P.: Offerings Retired: 1976 -- Scammel, Michael (Box 276)
  - French Language Authors, Publishers and Agents
    - L'Abbaye de Saint-Andre: 1979 -- Aries, Philippe: 1960-1981 -- Arthaud: Clebert -- Arthaud: Decareaux -- Arthaud: Fabre-Luce -- Arthaud: Lachoque -- Aubier: Offerings: 1981 -- Aubier: Other: 1981 -- Avon Play Anthology -- Bataille, Georges -- Beauchesne: 1975 -- Bloch-Laine, Francois -- Bremond, D'Ars, Yvonne (Box 277)
    - Brunhoff, Laurent -- Cerf, Geffre -- Cesaire, Aime -- Cocteau, Jean -- Delpire, Genie du Lieu -- Denoel: 1978-1979 -- Derrida -- Desclee de Brouwer: 1979 -- Desclee de Brouwer: Offerings: 1981 -- Desclee de Brouwer: Symoposia -- Desnos, Robert -- L'Express: 1981 (Box 278)
    - Fayard: 1971-1978 -- Fayard: Offerings: A-Z: 1982 -- Flammarion: Offerings: 1981 -- Flammarion: Sagan: 1975 -- Flammarion: 1978-1979 (Box 279)
    - French Permissions: A-Z -- French Permissions: By Author: A-Z: 1980 -- Gallimard: 1975 (Box 280)
    - Gallimard: 1976-1979 -- Gallimard: Offerings: 1979 (Box 281)
    - Gallimard: Offerings: 1981-1983 -- Gallimard: Sartre: 1964-1974, 1977 -- Grasset: Nizan -- Grasset: Ramuz -- Grasset: Rochefort 1963 -- Grasset: Souchere (Box 282)
    - Guerdan, Rene -- Guitton, Jean -- Hachette: 1967, 1969, 1971-1973 -- Hachette: Bonzon (Box 283)
    - Hachette: Daily Life: 1967-1970 -- Hachette: Frederix -- Hachette: Jullian -- Hachette: Offerings: 1966, 1968, 1983 -- Hachette: Picard -- Hachette: Restiff -- Hachette: Sorre (Box 284)
    - Hachette: Inquiries: 1967-1968 -- Intermonde Press -- Editions J'Ai Lu: 1973 -- Julliard: 1967-1973 (Box 285)
    - Julliard: Anglade -- Julliard: Arnaud -- Julliard: (Bougois) Breillat -- Julliard: Gilles -- Julliard: Gouze -- Julliard: Lifar -- Julliard: Loverdo -- Julliard: Massignon -- Julliard: Neveux -- Julliard: (Laffont) Nogueres -- Julliard: Offerings: 1966, 1971, 1973-1974 -- Julliard: Perec -- Julliard: Ponchaud, F. -- Julliard: Revel -- Julliard: Rodriguez -- Julliard: (Bourgois) Segre (Box 286)
    - Julliard: Servin -- Julliard: Weingarten -- Kessel, Joseph: 1968-1974 -- Kramer -- La Farandole: 1973 -- Laffont: 1969-1973 -- Laffont: Levy-Tillard -- Laffont: Masry -- Laffont: Masson: 1968 -- Laffont: Nogueres: 1964 -- Laffont: Robichon (Box 287)
    - Lapautre, Michelle: 1983 (Box 288)
    - Lapautre: 1984: A-Z -- Lapautre: Grossman -- Lapautre: Memmi -- Lavaivre, Noelle -- Lefebvre, Georges -- Lepp, Ignance: 1966-on, 1970-1971 -- Malaquais, Elizabeth -- Mandiargues: 1968 -- Mannoni, Maud: 1968-1974 -- Maritain: 1973 -- Maspero: Daubier, Jean -- Maspero: Elek, Helene -- Maspero: Emmanuel -- Maspero: Geries and Lobel -- Maspero: Gernet -- Maspero: Hussein -- Maspero: Jalee, Pierre -- Maspero: Camintau, Cleopas (Box 289)
    - Maspero: Laroui -- Maspero: Lowy, Michel -- Maspero: Nizan -- Maspero: Offerings: 1980-1982, other -- Maspero: Rosmer, Alfred -- Maspero: Sinelnikoff -- Mauriac, Francois: 1967 -- Maurois, Gerald -- Maurois, Michelle -- Mercure de France: 1965-1974 -- Mercure de France: Doubrovsky -- Merle, Robert: 1976- -- Duchess of Mesina, Sidonia (Box 290)
    - Albin, Michel: 1982-1985 -- Minuit: Amin -- Minuit: Axedos -- Minuit: Benveniste -- Minuit: Broue et Temine -- Minuit: Castelain -- Minuit: La Gangrene -- Minuit: Leuliette -- Minuit: Lewin -- Minuit: Morrissette -- Minuit: Offerings: 1971-1973 (Box 291)
    - Minuit: Offerings: 1974-1975, 1977, 1979, 1981-1983 -- Minuit: Miscellaneous, French -- Minuit: Pinget -- Minuit: Robbe-Grillet: 1973 (Box 292)
    - Minuit: Textbook Editions -- Minuit: Wittig: 1974, other -- Montaurier, Jean -- Monteilhet, Hubert: 1971-1972 -- Morin, Edgar: 1965-1973 -- Mosca Offerings: 1978 (Box 293)
    - Le Nouvelle Observateur: 1970, 1972-1973, other -- Oraison (Box 294)
    - Pauvert: 1971-1973 -- Pauvert: Belhomme -- Pauvert: Belleroche -- Pauvert: Darien -- Pauvert: Faure -- Pauvert: Henry -- Pauvert: Picard -- Pauvert: Sade -- Pauvert: Sadut -- Pauvert: Sarrazin -- Payot: 1973-1976 -- Payot: Grunberg, Bella -- Payot: Dumezil (Box 295)
    - Payot: Haim -- Payot: Nacht -- Payot: Offerings: 1972-1974, 1977 -- Payot: Pages -- Payot: Sebag -- Piaget: 1969-1973 -- Plon: 1968-1970 (Box 296)
    - Plon: Carrouges -- Plon: De Villiers: 1973-1974 -- Plon: Heuvelmanns: thru 1972, 1975 -- Plon: Katcha: 1975 -- Plon: Latil and Rivoire: 1975 -- Plon: Lavelle -- Plon: Leroy -- Plon: Levi-Strauss: thru 1973 -- Plon: Montherlant: 1968 -- Plon: Offerings: 1973-1974 -- Plon: Rheims -- Pont Royal: Cent Mille and de vie Quotidienne -- Pont Royal: Grands Voiliers Autor du Monde (Box 297)
    - Pont Royal: Saulnier -- Pont Royal: Terre des Empereurs -- Presses Universitaires de France: 1967, 1971 -- Renault, Maurice -- Rivoyre, Christine de -- Robert: 1964-1973 -- Rossignol, Jean: 1969 -- Seghers: 1968, 1970-1971 (Box 298)
    - Seghers: 1973 -- Seghers: Sainteny -- Seghers: Serguine, Jaques -- Seghers: Weinberg -- Seuil: Abdel-Malek -- Seuil: Aycoberry, Pierre -- Seuil: Atlan -- Seuil: Auclair -- Seuil: Barthes: 1963-1973 (Box 299)
    - Seuil: Barthes: 1974 -- Seuil: Beau -- Seuil: Beauregaru, O. Costa de -- Seuil: Bouillard -- Seuil: Bouleau -- Seuil: Boulez -- Seuil: Calvez -- Seuil: Cayrol -- Seuil: Chaix, Marie -- Seuil: Charon -- Seuil: Decoin -- Seuil: Devillers (Box 300)
    - Seuil: Domingo -- Seuil: Dormann -- Seuil: Dufrenne -- Seuil: Dumazedier -- Seuil: Dumitriu: 1970 -- Seuil: Dumont: 1964-1973 -- Seuil: Esmein -- Seuil: Estang -- Seuil: Fakinos -- Seuil: Finas -- Seuil: Frank, Christopher -- Seuil: Gattegno, Jean -- Seuil: Genette (Box 301)
    - Seuil: Glenans -- Seuil: Godart -- Seuil: Gutelman (Lamberti) & Lamour -- Seuil: Herbert -- Seuil: Held -- Seuil: Huguenin -- Seuil: Jean -- Seuil: Jeannin -- Seuil: Jeanson -- Seuil: Journal d'un Geurillero -- Seuil: Kristeva, Julia -- Seuil: Landsberg, P.L. -- Seuil: Laurentin (Box 302)
    - Seuil: Leboyer, Frederick -- Seuil: Leon, Dufour -- Seuil: Le Porrier: 1975- -- Seuil: Magny -- Seuil: Marighela -- Seuil: Marrou -- Seuil: Mende, Tibor -- Seuil: Microcosme: 1971 -- Seuil: Mus, Paul -- Seuil: Neher, Andre (Box 303)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1967: A-Z, 1968: A-Z, 1969: A-Z (Box 304)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1970: A-Z, 1971: A-Q, 1972: A-Z (Box 305)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1973: A-Z, 1974: A-Z, 1975: A-Z (Box 306)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1976: A-Z, 1977: A-Z, 1978: A-Z (Box 307)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1979-1981: A-Z (Box 308)
    - Seuil: Offering: 1982: A-Z, 1983: A-M (Box 309)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1983: N-Z, 1984: A-Z, Jan.-Dec. 1978 (Box 310)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1979-1980 (Box 311)
    - Seuil: Offerings, 1981/1982 January-December (Box 312)
    - Seuil: Offerings, 1983, Jan-Dec.; 1984, July-Dec. (Box 313)
    - Seuil: Ouologuem -- Seuil: Offerings: A-M -- Seuil: Petire Planette -- Seuil: Plyushch, Leonid -- Seuil: Revolte Etudiante -- Seuil: Riche -- Seuil: Rideau -- Seuil: Roguet (Box 314)
    - Seuil: Romanowicz -- Seuil: Rosnay -- Seuil: Salomon -- Seuil: Saporta -- Seuil: Sauvageot -- Seuil: Schwartz-Bart: 1967-1973, other -- Seuil: Schwoebel -- Seuil: Senghor: 1972 -- Seuil: Six -- Seuil: Solfeges -- Seuil: Struve -- Seuil: Todorov: 1972 (Box 315)
    - Seuil: Uribe, Armando -- Seuil: Vidal-Naquet, P. and Schnapp, A. -- Seuil: Villalonga -- Simoen: 1978 -- Societe des Auteurs: 1971-1972- -- Starobinski -- Steinman, Jean -- Table Ronde: Anouilh -- Table Ronde: Bodin -- Table Ronde: Dali -- Table Ronde: De Carmoy -- Table Ronde: Offerings: 1979 (Box 316)
    - Table Ronde: Saint Pierre -- Table Ronde: Troyat -- Table Ronde: Whitehead Agency -- Teilhard de Chardin -- Temps Modernes -- Terrain Vague: Socratos -- Terrain Vague: Sternberg -- Terrain Vague: Other -- Tisne: 1970 -- Tisne: Bussy: Claude-Lafontaine -- Tisne: Guide Artistique de la France -- Tisne: Delabesse -- Tisne: Frere -- Tisne: Napoli -- Touraine (Box 317)
    - Translators -- Troyat: thru 1973 -- Valensin -- Vermes: French Poster Book -- Wailly, Philippe de: 1974 -- Yourcenar, Marguerite: 1974 -- Wesmael: Charlier -- Ziegler, Jean: 1970 (Box 318)
  - Other Foreign Agents, Authors and Rights
    - Agenzia Literaria (Italy): Linder: 1983 -- Balcells, Carmen: 1983-1984: A-Z -- Bloch: 1984 -- Brasil -- Brazil: 1983: Schindler-Bloch (Box 319)
    - Japan Uni Agency: 1984 -- Leresche: Foreign Rights: 1976 -- Mohrbooks (Germany): 1983-1984, A-Z -- Rombach: 1983 (Box 320)
    - Rombach: 1984 -- Sane, L.: Scandinavia, other -- Smith, Lawrence: 1974 -- Tuttle: 1983 -- Tuttle-Mori: 1982 (Box 321)
- Series VI: 1971-1986
  - English Language Authors, Publishers, Agents and Subjects
    - Adams, Jane: 1980 -- Albery, Nabuko Uenishi -- Allen, Paul -- American Contracts: 1986 -- American Motion Pictures: 1983 -- American Publishers: General (Box 322)
    - American Publishers: General: 1984-1986 -- Appelfeld, Aharon: 1985 -- Asprey, Robert: 1982-1983 -- Aynor, H.S. -- Barrymore, Elaine -- Bat-Heim, Hadassah -- Batterberry, M. and A. -- Bellamy, Joe David -- Benedikt, Michael: 1980 -- Benson, Dennis: 1973 (Box 323)
    - Bing, Elizabeth: 1980 -- Blue, Adrienne: 1979 -- Bloom, Marc: 1983 -- Braman, Norman: 1980 -- Brecher, Michael -- Buckman, Peter: Rogers, Deborah: 1972-1974 -- Coleman, Libby: 1979 -- Collier, James: 1981 (Box 324)
    - Copyright Information: Aug. 1980- -- Cunningham, Anne Marie: 1981 -- Danto, Arthur C.: 1978, 1980 -- Dasheff and Dearborn: 1980 -- Denham, Alice: 1982 -- Derber, C.: Boston Nuclear Study Group: 1984 -- Drexler, Rosalyn: 1980 (Box 325)
    - Elliott, George P.: 1976-1977 -- The English Agency: 1986, other -- English, Fanita -- Epstein, Joseph: 1975, 1977-1978, 1980, other (Box 326)
    - Fackenheim, Emil: 1980-1981 -- Falk, Candace -- Farber, Thomas -- Fenisong, Ruth -- Frankel, William: 1977 -- Freedman, Ralph: 1979-1980 -- Friedman, Maurice: 1979-1980 -- Gardner, John: Serial and Magazine Rights Permissions: 1980 -- Gardner, John: Foreign Rights: 1980 (Box 327)
    - Gaylin, Willard: 1981-1982 -- Hastings Center: 1979 -- Gilder, George: 1979-1980 -- Gilliatt, Penelope: 1982 -- Gingold, Alfred -- Gold, Vera: 1973-1980 (Box 328)
    - Gordon, Diana: 1979 -- Hochstein, Rolaine: 1983 -- Levison, Andrew: 1980-1981 -- Logan, Elizabeth: 1979 -- Madden, David: 1978 -- Malone, John: 1980-1981 (Box 329)
    - Manning, Jack: 1979-1980 -- Mellen, Joan: 1986 -- Miscellaneous: 1984-1985 (Box 330)
    - Miscellaneous: 1986-1987 -- Mitchell, Joyce: 1981 -- Morris, Mary: 1979 (Box 331)
    - Mortimer, Penelope: 1974-1979 -- Newman, Leslie: 1976 -- Norman, Derek and Ursule -- Old Foreign Rights Lists -- O'Brien, Gerald F. -- Owens, Iris: 1982-1983 (Box 332)
    - Passantino, Claire: 1983 -- Pell, Eve -- Peterson, Paula -- Podhoretz, Norman -- Price, Johnathan: 1975 -- PW: Articles on Foreign Markets -- Ramati, Alexander -- Rieber, Robert: 1975-1976 -- Rogan, Barbara: 1984 (Box 333)
    - Rogan, Helen: 1978-1980 -- Rogers, Deborah: 1984 -- Rosenblum, Gail and Muske, Carol -- Roth, Oscar: 1976-1979 -- Rubenstein, Hillary: 1985 -- Rutherford, Douglas -- Sanders, Beverly: 1979 -- Schaeffer, Leah: 1975 -- Schwartz, Marian: 1982 (Box 334)
    - Scott, Peter Dale: 1979 -- Shapiro, Sidney: 1979-1984 -- Simon, Richard Scott: 1980: A-F, 1985: A-M (Box 335)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: 1985: N-Z, 1986 A-Z -- Simon, Richard Scott: Ash, Timothy Garton: 1983 (Box 336)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: Glazebrook -- Simon, Richard Scott: Grant-Adamson, Lesley: 1984 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Hill, Susan: 1983-1986 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Llewelyn, Sam: 1983 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Hunter, Vic and Lanny: 1986 -- Simon, Richard Scott: O'Brian, Patrick: 1978-1982 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Offerings: 1987: A-M -- Simon, Richard Scott: Perriam, Wendy: 1983 (Box 337)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: Petrie, Graham: 1982 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Reports: thru 1987 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Slaughter: 1979-1982 -- Simon: Thorpe -- Singer, Dorothy and Jerome: 1980-1981 -- Soho Charcuterie:1983 -- Stewart, Natacha: 1979 -- Stillman, Beatrice -- Templeton, Charles: 1982 -- Tumin, Melvin: 1978 -- Urdang, Constance -- Varble, Stephen (Box 338)
    - Vernon, V.: Butterworth: 1980-1982 -- Vincent, Peter -- Wiseman, Thomas: 1978 -- Ward, Robert: 1976 -- Warner, Dennis: 1976 -- Watt, A.P.: Alter, Stephen: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Anthony, Evelyn: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Berman, Chaim: 1980 (Box 339)
    - Watt, A.P.: Bitov, Oleg: 1984 -- Watt, A.P.: Brandon, Ruth: 1985 -- Watt, A.P.: Cammel, Michael: 1982 -- Watt, A.P.: Carr, J.L.: 1982 -- Watt, A.P.: Charlesworth, Monique: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Children's Books -- Watt, A.P.: Crispin, Edmund: 1982 -- Watt, A.P.: Crofts, Freeman Willis: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Freeman, R. Austin: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Freeman, R. Austin: Estates for Possible Reprinting Watt, A.P.: Freeman, R. Austin: Offerings (Box 340)
    - Watt, A.P.: General: 1987-1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Gilbert, Martin: 1985 -- Watt, A.P.: Graves, Robert and O'Prey, Paul: 1985 -- Watt, A.P.: Hamilton, Elizabeth: 1980 -- Watt, A.P.: Hare, Cyril: 1982-1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Hill, Reginald: Correspondence and Publishers: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Hill, Reginald: Movies and Reviews: 1986 (Box 341)
    - Watt, A.P.: Hillier, Bevis: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Hope, Christopher: 1987 -- Watt, A.P.: Knox, Ronald: 1983 -- Watt, A.P.: Ladenis, Nico: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: McCarthy, Patrick: 1980-1981 -- Watt, A.P.: Maddox, Brenda: Reviews: 1987-1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Maddox, John -- Watt, A.P.: Mason, A.E.W. (Box 342)
    - Watt, A.P.: Menuhin, Yehudi: 1985 -- Watt, A.P.: Middlebrook, Martin: 1982 -- Watt, A.P.: Morley, John David: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Mosiman, Anton: 1984, 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Murry, John (Richard Cowper): 1985 Watt, A.P.: Norris, William: 1982 -- Watt, A.P.: Offerings: A-L (Box 343)
    - Watt, A.P.: Offerings: N-R, 1984: S-Z -- Watt, A.P.: Phipson, Joan: 1985 -- Watt, A.P.: Pinney, Rachel: 1982 -- Watt, A.P.: Polland, Madeline: 1987-1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Postgate, Raymond: 1985 -- Watt, A.P.: Price, Anthony: 1981 -- Watt, A.P.: Rubinstein, Helge: 1982, 1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Rubinstein, Hilary: 1987 (Box 344)
    - Watt, A.P.: Rubenstein, Hilary: 1981 -- Watt, A.P.: Scammel, Michael: 1985, 1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Sherwood, John: 1986 -- Watt, A.P.: Sprigge, Elizabeth: 1982 -- Watt, A.P.: Swift, Graham: 1985, 1987-1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Waddington, C.H.: -- Watt, A.P.: Walker, Martin (Box 345)
    - Watt, A.P.: Walton, Lady Susana: 1986, 1988 -- Watt, A.P.: Young, Michael: 1985 -- Watt, A.P.: Yoxen, Edward -- Websters, H.and J. -- Winegarten, Renee: 1972-1975 -- Winn, Marie: 1977 -- Yale: 1979 (Box 346)
  - French Language Authors, Publishers and Agents
    - Fasquelle: Xerox -- Fayard: 1984-1985 -- Fayard: Attali, Jaques: 1985-1986 -- Fayard: Offerings: 1984: A-M, 1985-1986: A-Z (Box 347)
    - Flammarion: 1984 -- Flammarion: Offerings: 1984 -- Gallimard: Butor: 1972-1973 -- Gallimard: 1983-1984 -- Gallimard: Editions: 1985 (Box 348)
    - Gallimard: Offerings: 1985-1986, other -- Grasset: 1978, 1984 -- Julliard: 1974-1976 -- L'Express: 1985 -- Lapautre: 1982: A-Z, 1985: A-M (Box 349)
    - Lapautre: 1985: N-Z, 1986: A-Z -- Leboyer: 1981-1983 -- Albin, Michel: Offerings: 1984-1985 -- Minuit: 1985 (Box 350)
    - Minuit: 1984 -- Minuit: 1984Offerings: 1984 -- Miscellaneous: French: 1982 -- Mosca, Marie-Ange: 1978 -- Nouvelle Observateur: 1979 (Box 351)
    - Paurvet: Offerings: 1979 -- Paurvet: 1974 -- Payot: 1970 -- Payot: Correspondence: 1971-1972 -- Payot: Offerings: 1972 -- Philips, Kathe: 1983 -- Plon: Offerings: 1972 -- Sebag, Lucien -- Seghers: Offerings -- Seuil: 1985: Jan.-Jun. (Box 352)
    - Seuil (July-December 1983 - A-Z 1985) (Box 353)
    - Seuil: Offerings: 1986: L-Z -- Strassova: 1958 -- Vian, Boris: to 1976 (Box 354)
  - OTHER FOREIGN RIGHTS and AGENTS
    - Ali: 1984-1986 -- Balcells: 1985: A-M (Box 355)
    - Balcells: 1986: A-Z -- Bloch: 1985-1986 -- Japan Uni: 1985-1986 -- Mohrbooks: 1985: A-Z, 1986: A-M (Box 356)
    - Mohrbooks: 1986: N-Z -- Plessl: 1983 -- Rogan: Israel: 1983 -- Rombach: 1985-1985 -- Sane: 1985-1986 -- Tuttle-Mori Agency: 1986 -- Tuttle: 1985 (Box 357)
  - MANUSCRIPTS
    - Gardner, John Stillness and Shadows -- Original setting copy & Master setting copy (Box 358)
    - Gardner, John Stillness and Shadows -- Page Proofs (blue) & Page Proofs (black) (Box 359)
- Series VII
  - Authors and Agents, A-Y
    - Aksyonov, Vassily: 1981-1982 -- Ali: 1987, 1988: A-Z -- Alter, Robert: 1974-1978 (Box 360)
    - American Publishers: 1987-1988 -- Asprey, Robert: 1978-1979, 1985-1986 -- Ashbery, John: Permissions: 1985 -- Astrachan, Anthony: 1984-1985 (Box 361)
    - Avallone, Dr. Leopold: 1983 -- Azerrad, Jacob: 1982 -- Balcells, Carmen: 1981-1982: A-Z, 1987: A-Z, 1988 -- Banks, Lynne Reid: Watson-Little: 1987 (Box 362)
    - Berman, Marshall: 1980-1981 -- Billington, James H.: 1979 -- Blonsky -- Bly, Carol: 1980-1981, 1985 -- Bly, Robert: 1984 -- Borchardt, Georges: 1987-1988 (Box 363)
    - Bloch/Schindler: 1987-1988 -- Bolt and Watson: Mann, Jessica: 1981 -- Wilson, Colin: 1982 -- Bok, Sissela: 1985-1986 -- Boorstin, Paul: 1975 -- Boyd, Blanche: 1980 -- Bowers, John: 1984-1985 (Box 364)
    - Brolin, Brent: 1981, other -- Brown, Frederick: 1976-1984 -- Butterworth, Michael: 1983 -- Chapin, Anthony: 1974 -- Charyn, Jerome: 1981, 1985 -- Chemical Bank: 1984 -- Ch'en, Li-Li -- Chowder, Ken: 1986 -- Cohen, Geula: 1979 (Box 365)
    - Collier, James: 1983 -- Collier, Peter: 1974-1975 -- Coover, Robert: Magazines: 1980 -- Rogers, Deborah: Correspondence: 1982--, 1984 -- Delaney, Paul: 1980 -- Des Pres, Terrence: 1976-- -- Drexler, Rosalyn: 1982 (Box 366)
    - Dunn, Robert: 1979-1982 -- Dutch Rights-Rombach: 1981-1982 -- Edson, Russel: 1976-1980 -- Eistein, Kurt -- Elliott, George P.: 1978 -- Fayard: 1986 -- Fagles, Robert: 1977-1979, other (Box 367)
    - Foreign Sales: 1982-1985 -- Foreign Rights: Fonda/Delsyer Correspondence with Bass, and Foreign Contracts Pending -- Fonda, Jane and Delsyer, Femmy: 1981 -- Friedman, Morice: 1981-1982 (Box 368)
    - Gaines, James R.: 1976-1980 -- Gallant, Mavis: Permissions: 1983-1984 -- Gardner, John: Movies, Radio, etc.: 1980-1981 -- Foreign Rights: 1981 -- Garrigues, Eduardo: 1981 -- Gloag, John: 1979 -- Gold, Ivan: 1980 -- Goldstein, Ruth: 1980-1984 (Box 369)
    - Greiff, Constance: 1981 -- Gruber, Howard: 1974-1975 -- Gerd Plessl Agency -- Greene, Elaine: Schon, Donald -- Harrington, Geri -- Hendin, Herbert: 1980 -- Hegesen, Sally: 1981 -- Henderson, David: 1980-1981 (Box 370)
    - Hofman, Paul: 1980 -- Horowitz, David: 1977, 1981 -- Hyman, Mary and Philip: 1979-1980 -- Hutchinson: General: 1987 -- Huxtable, Ada Louise: 1979 -- Israel, Peter: Agents, 1977-1979 (Box 371)
    - Japan Uni Agency: 1980, 1982-1983, 1987 -- Kaplan, Fred: 1979-1981 -- Katz, Jacob: 1980-1981 -- Kimball, Philip: 1984-1985 (Box 372)
    - Kramer, Mark: 1975-1980 -- Lapautre: 1988: A-Z, 1987: N-Z -- Lawner, Lynne: 1980 (Box 373)
    - Lawner, Lynne: 1981 -- Linder, Erich: 1981-1982 -- Le Carre, John: A Perfect Spy (Reviews: British, American, Canadian, etc.) -- Documents: 1982 -- Reviews -- Lennart: Sane: 1981 (Box 374)
    - Macksey, Kenneth: Watson-Little: 1985 -- Madden, David: 1980-1981 -- McElroy, Joan: 1978-1979 -- McElroy, Joseph: 1979-1981 -- Mellow, James: 1979-1980 (Box 375)
    - Miller, Tanya: 1986 -- Minuit: 1986 -- Miscellaneous: 1988-1989 -- Mohrbooks: 1987-1988: A-Z (Box 376)
    - Mohrbooks: 1981: A-Z -- Molinaro, Ursule: 1982 -- Morris, Sylvia: 1983 -- Movies: Miscellaneous: 1988 -- New Press: Lee, John Alan -- W.W. Norton File -- O'Neil, William: 1976-1977 -- Ostrovsky, Erika: 1979 (Box 377)
    - Podhoretz, Norman: 1980 -- Pope John Paul: Hutchinson: 1987 -- Peters, Joan: 1978 -- Passantino, Claire: 1985 -- Portugal: 1985-1986 -- Ravich, Diane -- Reid, Randall: 1981 -- Roazen, Paul: 1977-1979 -- Robinson, Steve -- Rodman, F. Robert Dr. -- Rogan, Barbara: 1982, 1986, other (Box 378)
    - Rogers, Thomas: 1981-1984 -- Rombach: 1987 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Bragg, Melvyn: 1987 -- Simon, Richard Scott: Correspondence: 1986-1987 -- Simon, Richard Scott: 1987: A-Z (Box 379)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: 1988: A-Z -- Sadoff, Ira: 1978-1980 -- Sanchez, Thomas: 1979-- -- Sane: 1987 (Box 380)
    - Sane: 1988 -- Sayle (UK): 1986 -- Schaff, Peter: 1979 -- Scott-Stokes, Henry: 1987 -- Selzer, Richard -- Seuil: Wel Sales to UK Publishers: as of Jan. 1986 -- Seuil: 1986: Jan.-Jun. -- Sillitoe, Alan: 1975 -- Silverstone, Barbara: 1982-1985 (Box 381)
    - Simon, Richard Scott: 1981-1982: A-Z (Box 382)
    - Singer, Dorothy and Jerome: 1985 -- Smith, Geoffrey: Watson: 1984 -- Soho Charcuterie: 1985 -- Spearman: Robinson, Lytle and general -- Stang, Sondra: 1985 -- Steinbach, Meredith: 1984-1985 -- Suvin, Darko (Box 383)